<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Working Gent]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Working Gent]]></description>
        <link>http://workinggent.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2016 21:32:56 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://workinggent.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[bio.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>bio.</h1><h2>Jordan Bill Kuznia</h2><p>In June of 2013 I started working with mens style at the Men's Wearhouse in Bismarck, North Dakota while I was attending the University of Mary. While working there I began developing my knowledge on the basics of mens fashion and style. Over the next two years I would continue to learn and explore the topic, all the while enhancing my personal style and wardrobe. In March of 2015 I moved to Fargo, North Dakota and worked at a local family owned store called Straus Clothing, which opening initially in 1879. While there I learned more about the foundations of style and a lot of the history and details of the mens clothing business from the Stern brothers who ran the store. I worked there until the owners retired and the store went out of business. Now I am taking all that I have learned and am working at Men's Wearhouse in Fargo, ND and am willing to work with you independently to create your ideal outfit or full wardrobe.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/33105c8594bbbe991a1ca9d0c88b27ac6501fe2d.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://workinggent.com/bio/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">699ea516-e1b6-41b7-80e7-a6c33f97e65f</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2016 21:32:41 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[5 Everyday Men’s Style Mistakes ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>5 Everyday Men’s Style Mistakes </h1><h2> one. suit buttons </h2><p>For a gentleman, style is one of his most important tools, and is a deeply personal aspect of who they are. While I do encourage you to stay true to your own style, there are certain things that you simply should not do. Your style tells people about you without you having to say a word, and if you aren’t dressed the part it’s going to come across that you don’t know what you are doing. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/c5e6b649a6c12096cbf759c5c7271e5e793bdb51.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://workinggent.com/5-everyday-mens-style-mistakes/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">229c959f-9b3d-404e-8c83-e1f52dd4cbff</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2016 21:28:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>